Here at the NFL annual meeting with
Broncos general manager George Payton.
George, let's start with the trade for
Jaylen Waddle. What stood out about
Jaylen when you evaluated him and why
was this the right move for the Broncos?
>> first of all, you dig into the
background, just the makeup, the
competitiveness, the teammate. We had a
lot, you know, we had some players in
our team that had played with him at
Alabama. And just doing the background,
that he would really, you know, fit into
our culture. And then then you turn on
the tape, you know, and he's one of the
more explosive uh players in the NFL,
yet he's an elite route runner, really
good after the catch, you know, he's a
matchup problem, he can play all over.
So, really excited about him. Big
picture, was it a priority going into
this offseason to find another offensive
playmaker?
>> Um yeah, I mean, I you know, just some a
more explosive element. You know, we
were looking for something unique to
come up and that was that was unique to
get a guy like him to to to fit, you
know, complement already a really strong
group. We like our group and and uh so,
he'll complement it. You mentioned the
group that was there, you retained a lot
of free agents, including starters like
JK Dobbins, Alex Singleton. How did the
philosophy reflect the belief that you
and coach Payton have in this roster?
>> Well, we've won a lot of games with
these players. We trust them, they fit
the culture, they fit the makeup, and
yet they're really good players. And so,
we wanted them back, that was the plan,
we executed it, and we feel really good
about it. Last one for you, George, the
draft is uh less than a month away. When
you don't have a first-round pick, how
much more important is the college
scouting process to make sure you're
hitting on the second round and beyond?
>> Yeah, we've done this before. I mean,
unfortunately, we've been in this
situation two other times. We've got two
All-Pro players in Benito and Mims, so
we feel really good about it. We have
great scouts and uh you know, look
forward to the process.